

CONTACT

www.pablonudel.com

pablonudel@gmail.com

<u>+</u> 33 6 70 64 48 25

O Toulouse, France

in pablonudel

pablonudel

LANGUAGES

Spanish French English

SOFTWARE

Visual Studio Code Adobe Photoshop Adobe Illustrator Adobe AfterEffects Adobe XD Blender

SKILS

Html 5
Css 3 & Sass
Tailwind
Bootstrap
Javascript
ReactJS
ThreeJS
NextJS
NodeJS
ExpressJS
MongoDB

SQL

Git

PABLO NUDEL

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

I have extensive experience in various creative disciplines, including Art Direction, Illustration, Motion Graphics, 2D Animation, Graphic Design, and Web Design, as well as in client management and overall project direction. Currently, I have focused on front-end development while continuing to expand my knowledge in this field.

EXPERIENCE

03/2022 - 06/2023 Web Builder & Design Project Associate

@ Luxury Presence

As a web builder, I created websites for luxury real estate agents and brokerages. This included implementing, configuring, and optimizing custom assets and components.

As a Design Project Associate, I performed QA, CSS improvements, tracking, feedback, and approvals in the stages leading up to site launch.

2007 - 03/2022 Freelance Art Direction, Illustration, Motion Graphics

& Graphic Design

Over several years, I managed and developed comprehensive projects for personal clients to which I've contributed my expertise in various design and visual arts domains. Additionally, I've integrated as a consultant to diverse teams within numerous audiovisual production studios, including: Turner International Argentina, Gazz, StoryStudio, Mandinga, Candela Creative Group and Gato.

Clients: MTV, Coca-Cola, TCM Channel, Citi Bank, Personal.

09/2004 - 04/2007 Project Manager of Multimedia Department

a IMC Comunicación

I carried out various multimedia projects, landing pages, microsites and product presentations. I collaborated in project management and team coordination.

Clients: Microsoft, Nokia, Pirelli, PwC.

06/2002 - 03/2004 Graphic Design

@ GR Group

Branding, Corporate identity, Editorial Design, Multimedia Design.

ACADEMIC EDUCATION

2001 - 2007 Graphic Design

@ Universidad de Buenos Aires Not finished (90% complete)

COURSES & CERTIFICATIONS

09/2021 - 11/2022 Full Stack Development

@ Coderhouse

HTML, CSS, Git, GitHub, Boostrap, Sass, SEO, Javascript, React, Node.Js, Express, API RESTFul, Websockets, MongoDB, SQL, Testing, GraphQL